// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers

let quesstsssions = [
    {
       "index":0,
       "id":869,
       "numb":28,
       "question":"Which of the following is used for implementing the late binding?",
       "answer":"Virtual Functions",
       "options":[
          "Operator Functions",
          "Constant Functions",
          "Virtual Functions",
          "Both A and B"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":1,
       "id":862,
       "numb":21,
       "question":"Which types of arrays are always considered as linear arrays?",
       "answer":"Single-dimensional",
       "options":[
          "Single-dimensional",
          "Multi-dimensional",
          "Both A and B",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":2,
       "id":849,
       "numb":7,
       "question":"The C++ language is ______ object-oriented language.",
       "answer":"Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
       "options":[
          "Pure Object oriented",
          "Semi Object-oriented or Partial Object-oriented",
          "None of the above",
          "Not Object oriented"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":3,
       "id":871,
       "numb":30,
       "question":"Which type of approach is used by the C++ language?",
       "answer":"Bottom-up",
       "options":[
          "Right to left",
          "Left to right",
          "Top to bottom",
          "Bottom-up"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":4,
       "id":845,
       "numb":2,
       "question":"Which of the following is the correct identifier?",
       "answer":"VAR_123",
       "options":[
          "$var_name",
          "VAR_123",
          "varname@",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":5,
       "id":851,
       "numb":9,
       "question":"C++ is a ___ type of language.",
       "answer":"Middle-level language",
       "options":[
          "High-level Language",
          "Low-level language",
          "Middle-level language",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":6,
       "id":852,
       "numb":10,
       "question":"For inserting a new line in C++ program, which one of the following statements can be used?",
       "answer":"\n",
       "options":"['\n', '\r', '(a+b)', 'None of the above']",
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":7,
       "id":847,
       "numb":5,
       "question":"The programming language that has the ability to create new data types is called___.",
       "answer":"Extensible",
       "options":[
          "Overloaded",
          "Extensible",
          "Reprehensible",
          "Encapsulated"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":8,
       "id":865,
       "numb":24,
       "question":"Which of the following can be used to create an abstract class in the C++ programming language",
       "answer":"By using the pure virtual function in the class",
       "options":[
          "By using the pure virtual function in the class",
          "By declaring a virtual function in the base class",
          "By declaring the virtual keyword afterward, the class Declaration",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":9,
       "id":858,
       "numb":17,
       "question":"Which of the following is the correct definition of sorting?",
       "answer":"Sorting is a type of process in which the data or information is ordered into a specific order. Example increasing orders, decreasing.",
       "options":[
          "Sorting is a type of process in which the data or information is ordered into a specific order. Example increasing orders, decreasing.",
          "Sorting information or data only in increasing order",
          "Sorting is a type of process in which data elements are modified or manipulated",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":10,
       "id":855,
       "numb":14,
       "question":"Which of the following gives the 4th element of the array?",
       "answer":"Array[3];",
       "options":[
          "Array[0];",
          "Array[0];",
          "Array[3];",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    },
    {
       "index":11,
       "id":870,
       "numb":29,
       "question":" Which of the following statement is correct about the C++ programming language?",
       "answer":"In C++, both the Static and Dynamic type checking are allowed",
       "options":[
          "In C++, both the Static and Dynamic type checking are allowed",
          "In C++, member function are allowed to be of the type canst",
          "In C++, Dynamic checking is allowed",
          "None of the above"
       ],
       "material":"cplusplus"
    }
 ]